Resume

Name:- Vivek V Bhosale
Profile:- Senior Analyst

Mobile No.:- +91 9518353763 Address:- Talwade, Pune, Maharashtra.

Email ID:- vivekbhosale2901@gmail.com

LINKED IN:- https://www.linkedin.com/in/vivek-bhosale-59385b193/

PROFILE SUMMARY: -

Working Professional with over 8 years of experience in different fields like Accounts Payable, Real Estate, E-Commerce, and Order Management and fulfillment. A team player and a highly motivated individual willing to learn new technologies

and methods.

TECHNICAL SKILLS:-

- SAP(Material Management).
- Salesforce (SFDC).
- Service Now (Ticketing Tool).
- CRM.
- Microsoft Excel.

WORK EXPERIENCE: -

<u>Solitaire – Real Estate Company</u> Designation:- Senior MIS Analyst

Tenure:- February 2023 to December 2023

Being part of the Sales MIS team responsible for preparing and sending reports and keeping track of client's payments.

- Demand and Reminder creation as per client's payment plan based on work completion milestones of commercial and residential projects.
- Maintaining Demand Raised, Audit, Due date, Total Due, and Collection report.
- Perform Mid-Month and month-end reconciliation of every ongoing commercial and residential project.
- Keeping track of client's payments according to their unit work completion.
- Sharing Payment Request Letters, Possession Letters, Maintenance Letters, and Reminder Letters as per defined timeline.
- Closely monitoring every site visit and maintaining a tracker of the same.
- All projects handled from booking till possession.
- Handled customer disputes as part of the customer escalation Team(CARE Team)
- Keeping track of New bookings, current bookings, and cancellations of commercial and residential projects.

Accenture Technologies Ltd. Bangalore

Designation:- Order to Cash Senior Analyst

Tenure:- June 2021 to September 2022

Part of the **Order Management and Fulfillment team**, responsible for **managing supply chain functions** - creating, processing, invoicing, and delivering sales orders using t-codes through SAP. **Roles and responsibilities included**:

- Sales Order Creation/Modification/Reconciliation, Invoice Creation, and Sales Order Delivery.
- Ensure have met Service Level Agreements (SLA) on timelines and with accuracy.
- Worked on Ship to and Bill to creation.
- Process reconciliation, delivery, and invoicing of the Sales Order as per request received from the Business Analyst and SPOC in Salesforce.
- Processing opportunities received in **Salesforce** and **HDF** within the given TAT.
- Maintain Exception, Quality, and Production tracker daily.
- Preparing **DTP** (**Desktop Procedure**) as per the requirement of the client.
- Completed mandatory engagement training through my learning portal.
- Handled basic reporting for the Team.
- Weekly client calls to discuss Process Updates, Suggestions, Challenges, and improvements.
- Worked on tools like Salesforce, SAP, and Ticketing Tool (Service Now).

Digital Age Retail PVT Ltd. (Firstcry.Com), Pune

Designation:- Senior Customer Consultant

Part of the E-Commerce Customer Support Team. Roles and responsibilities included:

- Worked on modification of Customer's e-mail ID, shipping address, and mobile number.
- Resolving customer queries through calls, chat boats, and e-mails.
- Identifying customer requirements regarding products and suggesting related offers.
- Escalation calls and email handling
- Handling irate customers and providing them with resolution.
- Maintaining KRAs like AHT, Quality, and Utilization.

Infosys Ltd.

Designation:- Senior Accountant

Tenure:- May 2014 to July 2019

Tenure:- October 2019 to August 2020

Part of the Procure to Pay (Invoice Processing) Team. Roles and responsibilities included:

- Ensure **timely processing of the invoices** and thus **timely payments** with the productivity of 80-100invoices per day. All **invoices** are approved as per company guidelines.
- Invoice clarification including interaction with purchasers, requisitions, and/or vendors.
- Re-routing of invoices as per the type and region matrix
- Raising proper queries to business in case of any issues in invoices processing and resolving the issues
- Recognize and communicate potential issues to the respective team in case of necessity.
- Contributed ideas and actions toward the continuous improvement of processes within the area ofinfluence.
- Supporting clients to ensure timely payment to the vendors by processing Invoices within a given TAT.
- Preparing and maintaining Minutes of Meetings (MOM) on time.
- Review and update the Standard Operating Procedure (SOP) every week.
- Handling clients and vendor e-mails as a priority.
- Processed Purchase orders (PO) and non-PO-based invoices for 26 different countries.
- Weekly call with the client to discuss current progress and new suggestions regarding process improvement.
- Handling Critical Vendor Invoices to get them processed within time and avoid any escalations.
- Processed language barrier invoices with the help of Lexi Logo Keyboard.
- Followed Tax guidelines as per region, SOP, and Vendor exception while processing an Invoice.

ACHIEVEMENTS:-

- Worked as a part of the Process Improvement and Process Harmonization Team.
- Processed 2000+ Invoices in a month with 99% accuracy.
- Appreciation Emails from Clients and Managers for completing tasks on time with 100% accuracy.
- Recognition received from Clients, Seniors, and Higher Management.
- Received awards I-Star, Star Performer, Best Email, and Extra Mile for best performance.
- Achieved KPIS like lowest AHT 90 seconds, 100% attendance, and 92% utilization.

ACADEMIC QUALIFICATION:-

- B. Com: 2014: Pratibha College of Commerce & Computer Studies: Pune University.
- H.S.C.: 2005: Maloji Raje Agricultural College, Phaltan, Satara: Shivaji University.
- S.S.C.: 2003: Mudhoji High School, Phaltan, Satara: Shivaji University.

PERSONAL DETAILS:-

- Date of Birth: 29th January 1988
- Marital Status: Unmarried
- Hobbies: Listening to music, Watching Movies, Singing.
- Languages Known: Marathi, Hindi, English.

Date:- Place:-